ACTWU's Textile Division Records 5619/038
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Bird's Eye Strike Local 1822 Fulton, NY, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Brawers Brothers Local 1733 Strike Paterson, NJ, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Birdair Structures, Inc. Strike Local 1906 Buffalo, NY, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Breneman, Inc. Local 20684 Strike Oswego, NY, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Buffalo Batt & Felt Corp. Strike Local 1095 DePew, NY, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Capri Textile Processing Co. Inc. Local 1483 Fall River, Mass., 1981 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Chromatex, Inc. Local 1944 Strike Hazelton, Pa., 1982-1985 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Clark-Cutler McDermott Co Strike Local 31-T Franklin, Mass., 1982 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Colecraft Mfg. Co. Local 49 Strike Buffalo, NY, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Colecraft Mfg. Co. Inc. Local 49 Strike Buffalo, NY, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Colonial Parking Inc. Local 2052 Strike, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Consolidated Textiles Ltd. Local 1664 Strike Alexandria, Ontario (Cornwall Joint Board.), 1980 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Continental Forest Industries Plant 738 Local 248 Durham, N.C., 1981 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- Cornwall Spinners, Ltd. Strike Local 1945 Cornwall, Ont., 1982 (Box 16, Folder 36)
- Courtaulds, Inc. Cornwall, Ontario. Local 779-T Strike, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 37)
- Craftex Mills, Inc. Local 1785 Strike Auburn, Pa., 1981 (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Delany & Pettit Industries Ltd. (Lear Siegler Operations) Local 1719 Ajax, Ont., 1980 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- DePoortere Corporation Local 1676 Strike Wilmington, N.C., 1983 (Box 16, Folder 40)
- Dover Stamping Co. Local 1483 Strike Fall River, Ma., 1982 (Box 16, Folder 41)
- Duro Finishing Local 1226-T Strike Fall River, Ma., 1983 (Box 16, Folder 42)
- Duro Finishing Corp. Local 1057 Strike Fall River, Mass., 1980 (Box 16, Folder 43)
- Easton Tufting Local 35 Strike Easton, Pa., 1982 (Box 16, Folder 44)
- Eddington Thread Local 33-t Strike, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 45)
- Eddington Thread Mfg. Co. Local 33 Eddington, Pa. Strike, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 46)
- Edwards Mfg. Corp. Local 494 Strike Augusta, Me., 1980 (Box 16, Folder 47)
- Emerson Textile Local 468 Chelsea, Ma., 1980 (Box 16, Folder 48)
- Emporia Foundry, Inc. Local 1622 Lock-out Emporia, Va., 1983 (Box 16, Folder 49)
- Euro Curtain Corp. Local 2343 Strike Cornwall, Ont., 1982 (Box 16, Folder 50)
- Facile Technologies Local 1733 Strike Paterson, NJ, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 51)
- Fasco Coated Products (Div of Packaging Systems Corp) Loc 1939 Orangeburg, NY, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 52)
- Felters, Co. Local 232 Millbury, Mass. Strike, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 53)
- Fidelity (Wayne) Local 1733 Strike Paterson, NJ, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 54)
- Fidelity Industries Local 1733 Strike, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 55)
- Flock Industries Local 1921 Strike Phillipsburg, NJ, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 56)
- GTI Corp (Clover Div.) Local 1917 Strike Tonawanda, NY, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 57)
- Gemco Tape Co. Inc. Fall River, Mass. Local 1483, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 58)
- Gold Mills, Inc. Local 1493 Pine Grove, Pa., 1981 (Box 16, Folder 59)
- Hackensack Bolt & Nut Co. Strike Hackensack, NJ, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 60)
- Hallmark Plastics Local 1617 Buffalo, NY, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 61)
- Harding Carpet Limited Local 1857 Strike Collingwood, Ont., 1981 (Box 16, Folder 62)
- Harris-Crestline (Duo Temp Div) Local 1126T Depew, NY, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 63)
- Headwear Div. Strike Herschel Mfg. Co. Local 17/5556H St. Louis, Mo., 1983 (Box 16, Folder 64)
- James Hunter Machine Shop Local 1280-T Strike North Adams, Mass., 1980 (Box 16, Folder 65)
- Industrial Plastics Local 1820 Strike Valley City, Ont., 1983 (Box 16, Folder 66)
- Jamestown Finishes, Div of Essex Chemical Corp. Local 1010 Jamestown, NY, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 67)
- Jefferies Processors Inc. Strike Local 2001 Philadelphia, Pa., 1980 (Box 16, Folder 68)
- Jockey International Local 2434 Strike Cedartown, Ga., 1982 (Box 16, Folder 69)
- KCL Packaging of Canada, Ltd. Local 986T Woodstock, Ont., 1980 (Box 16, Folder 70)
- Kawneer Local 1923 Strike Franklin, Indiana, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 71)
- Keystone Dyeing Co. Local 2001-T Strike Philadelphia, Pa., 1982 (Box 16, Folder 72)
- Klote International Strike Maryville, TN, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 73)
- Lehigh Valley Throwing Mills, Inc. Local 965T Strike Bethlehem, Pa., 1982 (Box 16, Folder 74)
- Leshner Co. Local 2297 Strike Cincinnati, Oh., 1980-1982 (Box 16, Folder 75)
- Leshner Corp. Local 2382 Strike Hamilton, Ohio, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 76)
- Ludlow Textile Local 652-T Strike Ludlow, Ma., 1982 (Box 16, Folder 77)
- Lynn Vinyl Plastics Corp. Strike Lynn, Ma., 1981 (Box 16, Folder 78)
- Magda Pak Local 35 Strike Phillipsburg, NJ, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 79)
- Mand Carpet Mills Local 99-T Strike Los Angeles, Ca., 1980 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- C.H. Masland Local 1882 Strike Atmore, Ala., 1980 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- C.H. Masland & Sons Local 1739 Carlisle, Pa, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Meiwa Co. Local 1781T Strike Charlotte, North Carolina, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Metal-Cladding, Inc. Local 1611 Strike No. Tonawanda, NY, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- McGinley Mills Local 35 Strike Phillipsburg, NJ, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Mohawk & Hudson River Humane Society, Inc. Org. Strike Menands, NY, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Moose River Mills Ltd. Local 1576 Acton Vale, Que. Cowansville Joint Board, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- New London Local 1706 Strike Newark, Delaware, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Nu-Method Dyeing & Processing Co. Local 2052 Union City, NJ, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- PPG Industries Local 1710 Strike Stockertown, Pa., 1980 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Paradise Mfg. Co. Local 99 Strike Los Angeles, Ca., 1981 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Peerless Rug Ltd. Local 1585-1 Acton Vale, Que. Cowansville Joint Board., 1980 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Peerless Rug Ltd. Local 1585-2 Acton Vale, Que. Cowansville Joint Board, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Pellon Chemotextiles Inc. Strike Local 1915 Cornwall, Ont., 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Penn Dyeing & Finishing Co. Local 1559 Pine Grove, Pa., 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- F.E. Plankenhorn Braid Wks. Local 1914 Williamsport, Pa., 1982 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Professional Pharmaceutical Corp. Local 2361 Montreal, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Puritan Sportwear Corp. Local 1701 Strike Duncansville, Pa., 1981 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Quincy Dye Local 1788 Strike Woonsocket, RI, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- R-M Industrial Products Strike Local 1836 No. Charleston, SC, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Recticel Foam Corp. (Bernel Foam Prods. Co.) Local 1644 Buffalo, NY, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Refrigerateurs Foster du Canada Ltd. Local 1626 Drummondville, Que., 1983 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- River Textile Printers Local 1057 Fall River, Ma., 1980 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Scientific Dye Works Brooklyn, NY, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Skydyne, Inc. Local 1410 Strike Port Jervis, NY, 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Sono-Therm, Inc. Local 1748 Strike Buffalo, NY, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Robert Soper Ltd. Local 1862 Strike, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Speedways Conveyors, Inc. Strike Local 1748 Buffalo, NY, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Springdale Canada, Inc. Local 1419 Valleyfield, Que., 1981 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Standard Dyeing & Finishing Local 1733 Paterson, N.J., 1980 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Standard Yarn Local 300 Strike Worcester, Mass., 1983 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Stern & Stern Huget Textiles Local 221 Hornell & Canisteo, NY, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- The Stewart Group Local 1591 Strike Ontario, Canada, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 34)
- Stonehenge Processors Local 1733 Strike Paterson, NJ, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 35)
- Stonehenge Processors Local 1733 Cedar Grove, NJ, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- Techniplast Local 1733 Strike Paterson, NJ, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 37)
- Toby Industries, Ltd. Local 1814 Strike Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 38)
- Shoe Division Strike Assistance Vulcan Corp. Brockton, Mass., 1983 (Box 17, Folder 39)
- Waveline, Inc. Local 77-A Fairfield, NJ, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 40)
- Woonsocket Spinning Co. Local 2351 Strike Charlotte, NC, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 41)
- Wyandotte Industries Local 120T Strike Waterville, Maine, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 42)
- X-Tyal International Corp. Local 1946 Strike Hudson, NY, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 43)
- Ackerman Mfg. Co. Local 1594 Strike St. Louis, MO, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 44)
- Affiliated Medical Products, Limited Local 1775 Strike Ajax, Ontario, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 45)
- Algro Knitting Mills Local 1363T Strike Milltown, NJ, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 46)
- Allen Industries Local 1896 Strike Richmond, VA, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 47)
- Allen Industries Local 1374 Strike Herrin, Ill., 1979 (Box 17, Folder 48)
- American Olean Tile Co. Local 1666 Strike Lewisport, Ky., 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 49)
- Ametek (Westchester Plastics) Local 1808 Nesquehoning, Pa., 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 50)
- Amstar (Div. American Sugar) Local 939T Strike Versailles, Ct., 1978 (Box 17, Folder 51)
- Anchor Dyeing & Finishing Local 208 Strike Philadelphia, Pa., 1977 (Box 17, Folder 52)
- Ashworth Plastic Products Co. Local 1057 Strike Fall River, Ma., 1978 (Box 17, Folder 53)
- Ashworth Bros. Co. Inc. Local 1201 Strike Fall River, Mass., 1977 (Box 17, Folder 54)
- Babbitt Bearing, Inc. Local 1947 Strike Syracuse, NY, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 55)
- Bemis Bag Co. Local 1439 Strike Flemington, NJ, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 56)
- Biddeford Textile Co. Local 1856 Strike, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 57)
- Blue Ridge Winkler Textile Co. Local 1445 Strike Bangor, Pa., 1977 (Box 17, Folder 58)
- Borden Co. Local 1296 Strike Haverhill, Mass., 1979 (Box 17, Folder 59)
- W.D. Byron & Sons Tannery Local 658T Strike Williamsport, Md., 1977 (Box 17, Folder 60)
- Caledonian Dye Works Local 208 Strike Philadelphia, Pa., 1977 (Box 17, Folder 61)
- Capital Plastics of Ohio Local 1901 Bowling Green, Ohio, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 62)
- Capri Textile Processing Local 1227 Strike Fall River, Mass., 1977 (Box 17, Folder 63)
- Cheshire Lab IPCO Local 1602 Central & South Jersey Jt. Board, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 64)
- Chromatex, Inc. Local 1944 Strike W. Hazleton, Pa., 1979 (Box 17, Folder 65)
- Clifton Yarn Mills Local 178 Strike Clifton Heights, Pa., 1978 (Box 17, Folder 66)
- Cohoes Fabrics Printers, Inc. Strike, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 67)
- Colonial Print Ink Co. Local 2052 Strike Union City, NJ, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 68)
- Cone Mills Corp. Granite Finishing Plant Local 1113T Haw River, NC, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 69)
- Curbell Plastic, Inc. Strike Buffalo, NY, 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 70)
- Dartmouth Woolen Co. Local 39T Strike Claremont, NH, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 71)
- Davies Can Company Local 1670 Strike Cleveland, Ohio, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 72)
- Doric Dyeing & Finishing Ltd. Local 1686 St. Jean, P.Q., 1979 (Box 17, Folder 73)
- Randall, subsidiary of Walter Kidde Co. Local 1766 Strike Pawtucket, RI, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 74)
- Downs Carpet Co. Local 80 Strike Philadelphia, Pa., 1977 (Box 17, Folder 75)
- Drico Industrial Corp. Local 1932 Clifton, NJ, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 76)
- Duro Textile Printers Local 1208 Strike Fall River, Ma., 1977 (Box 17, Folder 77)
- Dyers Strike NY NJ Metropolitan, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 78)
- ESB Inc. Local 1627 Strike Buffalo, NY, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 79)
- Eagle Knit Strike Shawano, WI., 1978 (Box 17, Folder 80)
- Fabknit Mills, Inc. Local 1895 Strike Allentown, Pa., 1979 (Box 17, Folder 81)
- Fairtex Mills, Inc. Local 1665 Strike Allentown, Pa., 1977-1979 (Box 17, Folder 82)
- Fitchburg Yarn Local 1307 Strike Fitchburg, Ma., 1978 (Box 17, Folder 83)
- Flexo Transparent, Inc. Local 49 Strike Buffalo, NY, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 84)
- Food Packaging Local 1878 Strike Xenia, Ohio, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 85)
- Gatewood Products Parkersburg, W Va., 1979 (Box 17, Folder 86)
- Gemco Tape Co., Inc. Local 1483 Fall River, Mass., 1979 (Box 17, Folder 87)
- Glendale Spinning Mills Ltd. Local 1070T Strike Hamilton, Ont. Canada, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 88)
- Globe Albany Belting Co. Local 1067T Buffalo, NY, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 89)
- Wm. Horn & Bro, Inc. Local 33 Strike Philadelphia, Pa., 1978 (Box 17, Folder 90)
- Imco Container Local 1598 Strike, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 91)
- Inmont Corporation Local 226 Strike Toledo, Ohio, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 92)
- Insul-Coustic Corp Local 1811 Strike Greenfield, Ind., 1978 (Box 17, Folder 93)
- International Webbing, Inc. Local 1564 Strike, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 94)
- Thomas Jackson Rope & Cordage Local 184T Strike Reading, Pa., 1979 (Box 17, Folder 95)
- Johnson & Johnson (Baby Products) Local 2269 Strike Skillman, NJ, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 96)
- Johnson & Johnson Local 1893 Strike, Park Forrest South, Ill., 1978 (Box 17, Folder 97)
- Keuffel & Esser Org. Strike, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 98)
- KUSS Corp. Local 1812 Findlay, Ohio, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 99)
- Keystone Rubber Products Corp. Local 1149 T Buffalo, NY, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 100)
- Kingston Spinners Limited Local 1881 Kingston, Ont., 1977 (Box 17, Folder 101)
- Lambeth Rope Local 1124T Strike New Bedford, Ma., 1978 (Box 17, Folder 102)
- Leedall Products Mfg. Co., Inc. Milltown, NJ, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 103)
- Leshner Corp. Local 148T Strike Hamilton, Ohio, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 104)
- Maremont Corp. Local 406 Strike Saco, Maine, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 105)
- Medina Anodizing Corp. Strike Brunswick, Ohio, 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 106)
- Meiwa, USA, Inc. Local 1781 Strike Charlotte, NC, 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 107)
- Metroware Shade Co. Local 1550 Strike Clifton, NJ, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 108)
- Minnesota Knitting Mills, Inc. Local 168T Strike Mendota Heights, MN., 1978 (Box 17, Folder 109)
- Munsingwear Locals 66,1254,1256,1269 & 1890 Minn. WI. Mich., 1979 (Box 17, Folder 110)
- Niagara Hobby Distributors, Inc. Local 1748 Buffalo, NY, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 111)
- North Bergen Piece & Dye Local 2052 Union City, NJ, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 112)
- Ohio City Manufacturing Co. Local 2352 Strike Ohio City, Ohio, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Pacific Columbia Mills Local 254T Columbia, S.C., 1978 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Local 254 Pacific Strike Columbia, SC, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Percy Kent Local 393 Strike Independence, Mo., 1977 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Permacel Tapes Local 1298 New Brunswick, NJ, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Phoenix Dye Local 1448 Strike, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Scancelli Print Local 1932 Strike Passaic, NJ, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Somerville Belkin Industries Local 1823 Strike Ontario, Canada, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Standard-Coosa-Thatcher Co. Local 1418 Strike Chattanooga, Tn., 1978 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Stern & Stern Local 221 Strike Hornell, NY, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Stonehenge Processing Co. Local 1733 Paterson, NJ, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Swan Finishing Co., Inc. Local 1483 Strike Fall River, Mass., 1977 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- T & K Mfg. Co. Local Organizing Findlay, Ohio, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Toledo Mattress Co. Local 226-A Strike Toledo, Ohio, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Troy Mills Local 1560T Strike Troy, New Hampshire, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Unarco Home Products Local 1861 Strike Paris, Ill., 1978 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Vasrette (Div Munsingwear) Strike Local 1905-T Memphis, Tn., 1978 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Wardwell Braiding Mach Co. Local 1198 Strike Central Falls, R.I., 1979 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Knitting Mills Local 1846 Strike Waynesboro, Pa., 1979 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- West Point Pepperell Co. Local 305 Strike Biddeford, Me., 1978 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Whitman Products Local 1712T Strike, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- New Zealand Trade Unionist Visit (Stanley Rodger), 1980 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- National Council of Senior Citizens, 1978-1982 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Sam Nocella Retirement Dinner Woodlawn, Maryland, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Newsletters Local Unions, 1978-1981 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- New York State Labor History Assn., 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Democratic Party Conference Memphis, 1973-1976 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- N.J. Democratic Legislative Campaign Committee Meadowlands, NJ, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- The Southern Poverty Law Center, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Politics ACTWU, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 30)
- Request for Political Contributions, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 31)
- ACTWU Politics, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 32)
- Political Contributions November Elections, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 33)
- Political Contributions Primary Elections, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 34)
- Democratic Part National Convention NYC, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 35)
- ACTWU Politics, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 36)
- Politics Bill Bass South Carolina, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 37)
- Politics Memphis Democratic Party Conference, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 38)
- Byrne, Brendan (New Jersey) Gubernatorial Campaign, 1977-1980 (Box 18, Folder 39)
- ACTWU Politics New York New Jersey, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 40)
- Politics- Frank Thompson, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 41)
- Progressive Alliance Dinner Dupont Plaza Washington, D.C., 1979 (Box 18, Folder 42)
- Progressive Alliance- clippings, news, etc., 1979 (Box 18, Folder 43)
- Progressive Alliance NYT AD, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 44)
- UAW Meeting on "New Alliance of Progressive Forces" Detroit, MI, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 45)
- Doug Fraser (UAW) Coalition Washington, D.C., 1978 (Box 18, Folder 46)
- Progressive Alliance Washington, D.C., 1979 (Box 18, Folder 47)
- Plant Closings- Legislation (Progressive Alliance), 1979 (Box 18, Folder 48)
- Progressive Alliance MISC, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 49)
- Progressive Alliance Sol Stetin- ACTWU, 1979-1981 (Box 18, Folder 50)
- Proposition 13 California, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 51)
- Passaic County Democratic Dinner West Paterson, NJ, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 52)
- Passaic County Democratic Club West Paterson, NJ, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  Tuesday May 26, 1981
- Passaic County Democratic Committee Paterson, NJ, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 54)
- Passaic County Democratic Party Panel WPC Wayne, NJ, 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 55)
- Passaic County Democratic Committee West Paterson, NJ, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 56)
- Ozzie Pellecchia Dinner Dance Westmont Country Club West Paterson, NJ, 1979-1981 (Box 18, Folder 57)
- Interview-John Lack, Vice President WCBS Radio, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 58)
- Radio IUD Meetings Multi-Unions Radio Campaign, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 59)
- ACTWU Media Programs Executed (Radio/TV/Films/etc), 1979 (Box 18, Folder 60)
- Tom Herriman Re: Media, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 61)
- Radio/TV potential for ACTWU, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- UAW Campaign- Radio Use in Organizing, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Riger, Morris Federal Appt. (Job), 1977-1982 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Americans for SALT, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Tax Reform- Prop 13, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Other Unions, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Weber Case, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- White House Conference, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Bill Worthy, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- 29th World Zionist Congress, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Irving Abramson - Off Payroll, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Harold Ackerman, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Notification of Change of Address, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Alaska Gas Pipeline, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Illegal Aliens, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Adamic, Louis (30th Anniversary), 1981 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- ACTWU Policy Anti-Inflation Program, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- William Becker, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Belgrade Meeting Conference on Security & Cooperation in Europe, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Black Enterprise "Threads of Discontent", 1978 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Brandzel, Sol Request for Carpet for Chicago Public Schools, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Brooks Brothers Organizing Campaign Meeting of ACTWU Leadership Paterson, NJ, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Brooks Brothers Rally Paterson, NJ, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Brooks Brothers, Paterson, NJ, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Big Business Day Minneapolis, Minn., 1980 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Big Business Day Tickets, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- New York City - H. Brown Big Business Day, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- David Chaney Memorial Service Detroit, MI, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Coalition for a Democratic Majority, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Committee for National Health Insurance, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Condolences, Congratulations, etc. [folder 1 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Condolences, Congratulations, etc. [folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Cornell University ILR School, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- Rutgers Law School Applications Theresa M. Dowdy (from DeNovellis), 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 34)
- Dissent Magazine, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 35)
- Economic Development Corp of NYC, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 36)
- Education General, 1974-1978 (Box 19, Folder 37)
- Employer's Payroll Tax Option (Social Security), 1979 (Box 19, Folder 38)
- Full Employment Week, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 39)
- Full Employment Week Indianapolis, Ind., 1979 (Box 19, Folder 40)
- Full Employment Act of 1976, 1975-1977 (Box 19, Folder 41)
- J.P. Stevens & Co. Joel Gay Misc/General, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 42)
- Luncheon for Sen. Heinz Ruhnau The Dardanelles Rest., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 43)
- Greetings to Other Unions, 1973-1977 (Box 19, Folder 44)
- Humphrey-Hawkins Bill, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 45)
- Hubert H. Humphrey, 1974-1978 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Industrial Shows: Memo on article on Wall Street Journal (re Deering Milliken and others), 1977 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Industrial Trades Union of America Woonsocket, R.I., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- International Foundation of Employee Benefit Plans Meeting San Francisco, Cal., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- IOEU General, 1970-1979 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- IOEU Express, 1978-1981 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- IOEU General, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- IOEU Contracts, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Independent Office Employees Union Agreement with ACTWU, 1977-1979 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- IOEU Wage Reopening, 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- International Textile, Garment, and Leather Workers Federation, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Jewish Museum, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Kennedy Trial, 1978-1980 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Theodore Kheel, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Legislation Plant Closings, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Labor Policy & Labor Sector Advisory Comm. General, 1977-1979 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- William Lubbers NLRB Post Letters of Support, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Emil Malizia, 1975-1980 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Visitors from Malta NYC, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Manpower Education Institute, 1970-1978 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Mergers Textile Mills, 1964-1969 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- David Monas Memorial Service Cornwall, Pa., 1980 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Money Market Washington Post, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- The Nation honors Carey McWilliams The Biltmore, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Administratorship Fall River Joint Board, 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Appointment of Administrator Fall River Joint Board - Bert Demers, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Administratorship Central Fall River Joint Board - Bert Demers appointed, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Greater Northern Textile Joint Board Hearing Officer Report, 1981-1983 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Chicago Joint Board Chicago, Ill. Administrator, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Chicago Joint Board Administratorship & Hearing Officer Appt., 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- Administratorship Mike Merola Locals 506 Boundbrook, NJ, 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Administratorship Nitro, W. Virginia, 1980-1983 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Local 9 Administratorship, 1979-1982 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Administratorship-Local 174T Charlton City, Massachusetts, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Appointment of Administrator Local 185 Dalton, Ga., 1980-1982 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Administratorship - John Harrison Local 186T Williamsport, Pa., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Administratorship/Local 253 Columbia, S.C. Earl Honeycutt, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Local 281 Administrator Don Warner Hearing Officer- Charles Sallee, 1978-1983 (Box 21, Folder 4)